otakukart.com 2018-06-29

# Terms & Conditions, Privacy & Cookie Policy - Otakukart

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@otakukart.com.

At www.otakukart.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.otakukart.com and how it is used.

**Analytics**

We’ve implemented Google Analytics based on Display Advertising (e.g.  Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting).

We and third-party vendors, including Google, will use this remarking information and data based on previous visits to our site to serve relevant messages across the web.

You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads).

Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**3rd party cookies**

We uses cookies on our websites in order to provide enhanced functionality to users, such as user accounts and saved preferences. We also use cookies to ensure that you see the most relevant ads and limit the number of times we show you the same advertisements.

If you continue to use this site, we’ll assume you are happy to accept these cookies. Some of the adverts carried on our websites are delivered by third party servers and in doing so they may leave cookies on your machine.

You may opt-out of these cookies by following these links:

MediaMind opt-out: <http://ds.serving-sys.com/OBA/Europe/Opt-out.aspx>

FlashTalking opt-out: <http://www.flashtalking.com/cookieOptOut.html>

MindShare opt-out: <http://www.mindshareworld.com/privacy>

**Email Collection**

On many of the www.otakukart.com web pages, users will find a form where they can enter their email address in exchange for a free eBook or more information on a certain topic. The email addresses that are collected will be added into a database and may be emailed with information, promotions, and any other content www.otakukart.com deems appropriate. Users may remove themselves from the email database at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” button that is found at the bottom of every email sent from www.otakukart.com.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.otakukart.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

This site uses cookies – small text files that are placed on your machine to help the site provide a better user experience. In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping carts, and provide anonymised tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics. As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at [the About Cookies website](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) which offers guidance for all modern browsers

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.otakukart.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to www.otakukart.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

**Google Adsense**

**Clickbank**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.otakukart.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.otakukart.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.otakukart.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**Sales & Discounts**

In the event that a product goes on sale or is subject to a discount, any customer who has purchased the product within the previous 7 days (and who can provide a valid receipt of purchase) will be entitled to a partial refund of the difference in price between the discounted price and the price the customer paid for the product.
